Md Shaharul Islam

Dhaka, Bangladesh



shaharulislam025@gmail.com

+8801777-492725

Summary

Good deeds increase interest in work.

Fey, Welcome! I enjoy turning ideas into reality through creative solutions.

FI specialize in HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Javascript, Builders.IcanConvert (PSD,Figma, XD,PDF,IMG,Sketch)ToHTML, EmailTemplateDesign.

 \square Oh yes of course I am a professional Fontant website designer.

ELet your design be beautiful, let your relationship be beautiful.

 $\hbox{$^{\square}$ Here is my portfoliowhere you will find all of my previous works and more details about me}$

☞https://

Experience



Web Designer

Fiverr Jun 2023-Present (10 months)



Freelance Jun 2023-Present

Web Designer

Upwork June2023-Present(1year1month)

Student

Jun 2022-Present

Education



Joypurhat Government College

Degree (Pass) 2021 - 2022

Licenses & Certifications



Fontant Web Development – Hablu Programmer

Issued 2023 - Expires Nov 2024

Skills

Front-endDesign · LandingPages · E-Commerce · PSDtoHTML · Bootstrap · HTML5 · CSS3 · FIGMATO HTML · IMGTO HTML